Inventory of the Papers of Judge John W. Bissell, 1983-2005
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
- Papers, 1989 (Box 17-21)
  - Jackson v. Mahler 1989 November 21 (Box 19)
  - Jayme v. Bd. of Veterans Appeals 1989 June 07 (Box 19)
    Military law
    Veterans' pensions and compensation
  - Jollister Shipping Corp. v. 3,000 Metric Tons of Granite Blocks 1989 October 03 (Box 19)
  - Kehoe v. Keister 1989 December 22 (Box 19)
    Opinion; Exhibits (2); Judgment
    Kehoe v. Keister, 727 F. Supp. 896 (D. N.J. 1989).
  - Kerollis v. U.S. Air, Inc. 1989 February 07 (Box 19)
    Opinion; Order │ Opinion (1989 June 12), Order
  - Kimberlin v. Craftmatic Comfort Mfg. Corp. 1989 February 02 (Box 19)
  - Lee v. Carey Canada, Inc. 1989 October 12 (Box 19)
  - Levitin v. Herman 1989 November 27 (Box 19)
  - Levinson v. Budd Foods 1989 December 01 (Box 19)
  - Lucy v. Am. Paper Sales 1989 July 12 (Box 19)
  - Lyons Capital Res. v. Rome Diagnostic Assoc. 1989 July 14 (Box 19)
  - Mack Boring Parts Co. v. Moffitt 1989 April 21 (Box 19)
  - Manfra v. Hertz Corp. 1989 January 17 (Box 19)
  - McQuestion v. N.J. Transit Rail Operations 1989 May 12 (Box 19)
  - Meneses v. Stephens 1989 August 24 (Box 19)
  - Mega Computer Sys. v. Remance 1989 June 14 (Box 19)
  - Midlantic Nat'l Bank v. Fed. Plaza Medical Assoc. 1989 August 04 (Box 19)
  - Metro. Steel Indus. v. Aetna Cas. & Sur. Co. 1989 October 12 (Box 19)
  - Millipore Corp. v. New Brunswick Scientific Co. 1989 December 01 (Box 19)
  - Mollett v. Frank 1989 January 25 (Box 19)
  - Monon Corp. v. Ctr. Serv. 1989 June 06 (Box 19)
  - Monarch Entertainment Bureau v. Newton 1989 February 02 (Box 19)
  - N. Feather Int'l v. Those Certain London Underwriters 1989 February 22 (Box 19)
    N. Feather Int'l v. Those Certain London Underwriters, 714 F. Supp. 1352 (D. N.J. 1989).
  - Oral Research Lab. v. L. Perrigo Co. 1989 June 23 (Box 20)
  - O'Reilly v. Specification Built Corp. 1989 February 22 (Box 20)
  - Panek v. Bagucz 1989 March 10 (Box 20)
    Panek v. Bagucz, 718 F. Supp. 1228 (D. N.J. 1989).
  - Parzen v. Petrie Stores Corp. 1989 February 02 (Box 20)
  - Patlex Corp. v. JEC Lasers 1989 November 27 (Box 20)
  - People's Bank v. Estate of Romanelli 1989 September 20 (Box 20)
  - Powell v. Arvonio 1989 November 20 (Box 20)
  - Remington Rand Corp. v. Business Sys., Inc. 1989 October 10 (Box 20)
  - Rittenhouse v. Fauver 1989 December 01 (Box 20)
  - Ryan v. Burlington County 1989 March 06 (Box 20)
  - Sahni v. Port Auth. 1989 June 28 (Box 20)
  - Savage v. Federated Dep't Stores 1989 May 02 (Box 20)
    Opinion; Order; Amended Order (1989 May 02)
    Savage v. Federated Dep't Stores, No. 88-4444, 1989 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 18129 (D. N.J. May 2, 1989).
  - Sayre v. Douglas Call Co. 1989 November 29 (Box 20)
  - Schoonejongen v. Curtiss-Wright Corp. 1989 November 06 (Box 20)
    Schoonejongen v. Curtiss-Wright Corp., No. 84-4542, 1989 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 18956 (D. N.J. June 22, 1989).
  - SDF Co. v. J.S. of Am., Inc. 1989 January 12 (Box 20)
    Opinion; Order; Order (1989 January 12); Order (1989 January 12)
  - Sgro v. Samna Corp. 1989 February 23 (Box 20)
  - Share Corp. v. Stevens 1989 June 19 (Box 20)
    Opinion; Opinion; Order (1989 June 30)
  - Sharplan Lasers v. WR Air Serv. 1989 June 29 (Box 20)
    Opinion; Opinion; Order (1989 October 02)
  - Shumate v. Piezo Elec. Prod. 1989 April 27 (Box 20)
  - Siciliano v. Div. of Youth & Family Serv. 1989 May 08 (Box 20)
  - Stackhouse v. Rafferty 1989 November 16 (Box 20)
  - Steinberger v. Ruggiero 1989 May 25 (Box 20)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1989 November 09)
  - Stiftung v. AmEuro Capital Corp. 1989 February 09 (Box 20)
  - Strassman v. Natsnax 1989 October 05 (Box 20)
  - Strickland v. Essex County 1989 June 16 (Box 20)
    Opinion; Order; In Forma Pauperis Application
  - Student Pub. Interest Research Group of N.J. v. Hercules 1989 April 06 (Box 20)
    Student Pub. Interest Research Group of N.J. v. Hercules, No. 83-3262, 1989 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 16901 (D. N.J. Apr. 6, 1989).
  - Supac Sys. v. Fastrax 1989 May 01 (Box 20)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1989 June 14)
  - Thomas v. Terumo Corp. 1989 December 15 (Box 20)
  - Thompson v. Passaic County 1989 May 12 (Box 20)
  - In re Tort 1989 January 19 (Box 20)
  - Trucking Employees of N. Jersey Welfare Fund v. LPC Trucking 1989 June 28 (Box 20)
  - 2175 Lemoine Ave. Corp. v. Finco 1989 April 27 (Box 21)
  - United States v. Tal 1989 April 21 (Box 21)
  - United States v. Branch 1989 March 20 (Box 21)
  - United States v. Fiorentino 1989 September 25 (Box 21)
  - United States v. Gambino 1989 January 17 (Box 21)
    Letter-Opinion; Judgment and Probation Order; Order
  - United States v. Mejia 1989 September 25 (Box 21)
  - United States v. Pray 1989 February 14 (Box 21)
  - United States v. Qualified Enter. 1989 June 26 (Box 21)
  - United States v. Silberman 1989 August 15 (Box 21)
    Opinion; Order; Letter-Memorandum
  - United States v. Sinacori 1989 May 12 (Box 21)
  - V.C. v. Hasbrouck Heights Bd. of Ed. 1989 May 25 (Box 21)
    Academic performance and assessments
  - Waigand v. Equal Employment Opportunity Program 1989 July 19 (Box 21)
  - Westinghouse Credit Corp. v. D'Annunzio Bros. 1989 May 19 (Box 21)
  - Youngs v. N.J. State Parole Bd. 1989 October 13 (Box 21)
- Papers, 1990 (Box 21-26)
  All papers dated 1990.
  - Alaikim v. Kennedy 1990 July 02 (Box 21)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order
  - Algea v. Sullivan 1990 December 05 (Box 21)
  - Allstate Ins. Co. v. Florio 1990 June 27 (Box 21)
  - Am. Cyanamid Co. v. S.C. Johnson & Sons 1990 March 05 (Box 21)
    Letter-Opinion; Opinion; Order
  - Banfield v. Middlesex County Adult Corr. Ctr. 1990 October 15 (Box 21)
  - Bel-Art Prod. v. Nalge Co. 1990 April 27 (Box 21)
    Bel-Art Prod. v. Nalge Co., No. 89-4054, 1990 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 19333 (D. N.J. Apr. 27, 1990).
  - Berkner v. Epstein 1990 July 02 (Box 21)
  - Bi-Coastal Investors v. Westreich 1990 August 23 (Box 21)
  - Bowater Commc'n Papers v. Kirsinger 1990 November 02 (Box 21)
    Opinion; Letter; Brief; Order; Amended Order
  - Bysterbusch v. Sec'y of Health & Human Serv. 1990 February 22 (Box 21)
  - Carteret Indus. Project v. Gen. Ins. Co. of Trieste & Venice 1990 August 01 (Box 21)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order
  - Castro v. State 1990 December 12 (Box 21)
  - Chambers v. Derwinski 1990 September 14 (Box 21)
  - Ciano v. American-Valve 1990 September 21 (Box 21)
  - C&K Builders v. N.Y. Life Ins. Co. 1990 January 22 (Box 21)
  - Conoco v. Tank Barge Interstate 36 1990 March 28 (Box 21)
  - Construction & Maintence Corp. v. PPD Prop. 1990 May 15 (Box 21)
  - Control Air v. Am. Trans-Freight 1990 May 14 (Box 22)
  - Cooper v. Hera Res. 1990 July 02 (Box 22)
  - Corsi v. Sullivan 1990 June 29 (Box 22)
  - CPC Int'l v. Int'l Ins. Co. 1990 January 22 (Box 22)
  - Di Felice v. Hoffmann-La Roche 1990 June 27 (Box 22)
  - Dole v. Int'l Matex Tank Terminals 1990 July 06 (Box 22)
    Industrial policy and productivity
  - Dole v. Int'l Union of Elec. Radio Workers, Local 427 1990 May 24 (Box 22)
    Voting rights
  - Equitable Life Assurance Soc'y of the U.S. v. Houston Gen. Ins. Co. 1990 March 28 (Box 22)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1990 May 18)
    Soil pollution
  - Elkins v. Spanoudis 1990 August 10 (Box 22)
    Private legislation
  - Enprotech Corp. v. Renda 1990 October 23 (Box 22)
    Opinion; Opinion; Order (1990 December 14)
    Income tax deductions
    Income tax deferral
    Income tax exclusion
    Income tax rates
  - Estate of Fiorilli v. N.J. Carpenters Health Fund 1990 April 26 (Box 22)
    Health programs administration and funding
  - Fasick v. Hilton 1990 January 23 (Box 22)
  - Federowicz v. Arvonia 1990 May 18 (Box 22)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1990 August 06)
  - Fineman v. Armstrong World Indus. 1990 August 23 (Box 22)
  - Firetek Corp. v. Nat'l Guardian Sec. Serv. Corp. 1990 May 11 (Box 22)
  - First Fidelity Bank v. Parness 1990 February 16 (Box 22)
  - Fleisher v. United States 1990 May 02 (Box 22)
    Opinion; Order; Letter (1991 January 29); Opinion, Third Circuit (1991 January 29)
  - Gen. Biscuit Brands v. R.K.D. Oil Co. 1990 October 15 (Box 22)
  - Gibraltar Plastics Corp. v. United Textile Workers of Am. 1990 September 18 (Box 22)
  - Gilliens v. Wilentz 1990 May 09 (Box 22)
  - Goldstein v. Windstream Int'l 1990 November 01 (Box 22)
  - Noeller Indus. v. Tri-State Dev. Co. 1990 April 05 (Box 22)
  - Hartigan v. Ins. Co. of N. Am. 1990 March 05 (Box 22)
  - Hayward Indus. v. Cole Indus. 1990 March 05 (Box 22)
  - Harris Corp. v. Int'l Rectifier Corp. 1990 November 26 (Box 22)
  - Hartford Fire Ins. Co. v. Elizabethtown Gas Co. 1990 October 05 (Box 22)
  - Henderson v. Beyer 1990 May 16 (Box 22)
  - Hochman v. Fypon 1990 October 11 (Box 22)
  - Hotel Employees Int'l Union Welfare Fund v. Pub of N.J. 1990 September 07 (Box 22)
    Opinion; Order [Cohen, Senior J.] [published]
  - Hunt v. Bellavia 1990 April 06 (Box 22)
    Emergency medical services and trauma care
  - Ingersoll-Rand Fin. Corp. v. Berenyi 1990 January 08 (Box 22)
  - Integrity Ins. Co. v. Whaley 1990 September 20 (Box 22)
    Opinion; Order; Order (1990 September 20)
  - Israelsky v. J.C. Penny Co. 1990 August 15 (Box 23)
  - Iwatsu Am. v. S. Telcom Corp. 1990 February 21 (Box 23)
  - J&A Coffee v. Gloria Jean's Coffee Bean Franchising Corp. 1990 June 29 (Box 23)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion (1990 September 17); Order Denying Reargument and Renewal; Order
  - Jacobs v. Beyer 1990 March 08 (Box 23)
  - James v. Supermarkets Gen. Corp. 1990 June 04 (Box 23)
  - Jenkins v. Sullivan 1990 October 16 (Box 23)
  - Kane Carpet Co. v. Ins. Co. of N. Am. 1990 March 27 (Box 23)
  - Karolis v. Neubert 1990 December 06 (Box 23)
    Organized crime
  - Kaufman v. Hoffmann-La Roche, Inc. 1990 June 25 (Box 23)
  - Kemp v. Hous. Auth. of Passaic 1990 February 08 (Box 23)
  - Killinger v. Krack 1990 August 23 (Box 23)
  - King Fisher Marine Serv. v. Hanson Dev. Co. 1990 June 04 (Box 23)
    Opinion; Order; Order Amending Opinion (1990 June 06)
  - Knodel v. State 1990 January 05 (Box 23)
  - Kochana v. Bonnick 1990 December 11 (Box 23)
  - Krowl v. United States 1990 August 16 (Box 23)
  - Levinson v. Budd Foods 1990 June 15 (Box 23)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion (1990 August 23); Order
  - Liberty Mut. Ins. Co. v. Jackson 1990 June 22 (Box 23)
  - Lombardi v. Hobart Mfg. Co. 1990 March 13 (Box 23)
  - Louis v. Foley Towlift, Inc. 1990 June 04 (Box 23)
  - Lowitt v. Sullivan 1990 September 18 (Box 23)
  - Marketforce Holdings Co. v. Arkell 1990 March 28 (Box 23)
  - Marotta Scientific Controls v. RLI Ins. Co. 1990 June 04 (Box 23)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion (1990 July 17); Order; Opinion (1990 October 16); Order
    Marotta Scientific Controls v. RLI Ins. Co., No. 87-4438, 1990 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 20167 (D. N.J. June 4, 1990).
  - Martinez v. United States 1990 May 31 (Box 23)
    Martinez v. United States, 743 F. Supp. 298 (D. N.J. 1990).
  - MCI Telecomm. Corp. v. Sutz 1990 September 20 (Box 23)
  - Melignano v. Roeslere 1990 September 25 (Box 23)
  - Merola v. Prudential-Bache Sec. 1990 January 23 (Box 23)
    Opinion; Order; Order Amending Opinion and Order (1990 January 30)
  - Merola v. Beyer 1990 June 29 (Box 23)
  - McNeil v. Nat'l Football League 1990 June 12 (Box 23)
    Opinion; Order; Order Amending Opinion (1990 July 03)
  - Miller v. Ahrenholz 1990 January 22 (Box 23)
  - Miller v. Sessions 1990 January 22 (Box 23)
  - Miller v. Nickolopoulos 1990 September 26 (Box 23)
  - Millipore Corp. v. New Brunswick Scientific Co. 1990 May 24 (Box 23)
  - Morgran Stiftung v. AmEuro Capital Corp. 1990 December 07 (Box 23)
    Liechtenstein
  - Morris v. Beyer 1990 May 21 (Box 24)
  - Morrison v. Sullivan 1990 July 10 (Box 24)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion (1990 August 13); Order
  - Moskowitz v. Ryan 1990 October 25 (Box 24)
    Department of the Treasury
  - Mullis v. Prudential Ins. Co. of Am. 1990 October 15 (Box 24)
  - Murphy v. Scheidemantel 1990 March 12 (Box 24)
  - Nat'l State Bank v. First City Nat'l Bank & Trust Co. 1990 August 23 (Box 24)
    Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC)
  - New Brunswick Sav. Bank v. Nw. Mortgage Co. 1990 August 15 (Box 24)
  - N.J. Transit Corp. v. Spentonbush/Red Star Co. 1990 June 27 (Box 24)
    Roads and highways
  - Nissei Elec. v. JV Distributing, Inc. 1990 June 13 (Box 24)
  - Novembre v. Diehl 1990 March 08 (Box 24)
    Opinion; Order | Opinion; Order Granting Summary Judgment (1990 April 17)
  - Pasternak v. Sullivan 1990 May 31 (Box 24)
  - Pellegrino v. Arvonio 1990 November 29 (Box 24)
  - Mid Jersey Trucking Indus., Local 701 v. Omni Funding Group 1990 February 15 (Box 24)
    Opinion (Opinion of U.S.D.J. Garret E. Brown, Jr.); Order
  - Peterson v. Doe 1990 September 28 (Box 24)
    Mining
  - Phillips v. Beyer 1990 February 28 (Box 24)
  - Plain v. Plain 1990 January 16 (Box 24)
    Literature
    Books and print media
    Art, artists, authorship
  - Porter v. Sullivan 1990 March 23 (Box 24)
  - Remington Rand Corp. v. Bus. Sys., Inc. 1990 April 01 (Box 24)
    Opinion; Order for Writ of Execution and Release of Registry Funds | Opinion (1990 April 20); Order; Order Approving Settlement Agreement (1989 September 25) (Order of U.S. Bankruptcy Judge Harold C. Abramson) | Opinion (1990 June 27) | Letter-Opinion (1990 September 13); Order
  - Reyner v. Grow Group 1990 April 24 (Box 24)
    Delaware
    Advanced technology and technological innovations
    Belgium
    United Kingdom
  - Ricardo Araya, Inc. v. Bel-Aire Ins. Co. 1990 April 18 (Box 24)
  - Rodriguez v. City of Passaic 1990 February 21 (Box 24)
  - Romac of Colorado v. Romac & Assoc. 1990 October 24 (Box 24)
    Labor and Employment
    Colorado
  - Rosa v. Resolution Trust Corp. 1990 December 05 (Box 24)
    Opinion (Opinion of U.S.D.J. Fisher)
  - Ryan v. N.J. State Parole Bd. 1990 February 27 (Box 24)
  - Sandom v. Travelers Mortgage Serv. 1990 December 20 (Box 24)
    Opinion (Opinion of U.S.D.J. Mitchell H. Cohen); Order
  - San Filippo v. Bongiovanni 1990 July 25 (Box 24)
    Science and engineering education
    Research ethics
  - Sayre v. Douglas Call Co. 1990 February 22 (Box 25)
  - Schoonejongen v. Curtiss-Wright Corp. 1990 August 23 (Box 25)
    Letter-Opinion; Order; Opinion | Opinion; Order (1990 December 17)
    Schoonejongen v. Curtiss-Wright Corp., No. 84-4542, 1990 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 20791 (D. N.J. Aug. 23, 1990); No. 84-4542, 1990 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 20792 (D. N.J. Dec. 17, 1990).
  - Share Corp. v. Stevens 1990 July 17 (Box 25)
  - Shephard v. Zelinski 1990 July 02 (Box 25)
  - Silverman v. CPC Chem. 1990 June 22 (Box 25)
    Opinion; Order | Opinion; Order (1990 November 07)
  - Smith v. State 1990 August 03 (Box 25)
  - Spencer v. Fauver 1990 July 02 (Box 25)
  - Spivey v. Stephens 1990 July 12 (Box 25)
  - Stackhouse v. Grier 1990 May 11 (Box 25)
  - Strazdas v. Brady 1990 March 15 (Box 25)
  - Sussex Drug Products Co. v. Kanasco 1990 February 22 (Box 25)
    Opinion; Judgment | Opinion; Order (1990 May 18)
  - Telepo v. Cardinale 1990 June 01 (Box 25)
  - Telepo v. Scheidemantel 1990 April 30 (Box 25)
    Opinion (Opinion of U.S.D.J. Clarkson S. Fisher); Order
  - Terrell v. Soc. Sec. Admin. 1990 October 25 (Box 25)
  - Timinski v. State 1990 June 07 (Box 25)
  - Toombs v. Citicorp 1990 May 15 (Box 25)
  - Travelers Indem. Co. v. Lab. Serv. 1990 November 09 (Box 25)
    Opinion; Order; Exhibit
  - Trewhella v. United States 1990 January 08 (Box 25)
  - Tuxedo Beach Club Corp. v. City Fed. Sav. Bank 1990 October 31 (Box 25)
  - Tyler v. Star Home Improvement Co. 1990 June 18 (Box 25)
    Opinion; Order | Opinion (1990 September 20); Order | Opinion (1990 November 09); Order
  - United States v. Acton Corp. 1990 March 28 (Box 25)
    Opinion (Opinion of U.S.D.J. Garrett Brown)
    Land use and conservation
  - United States v. Algon Chem. 1990 April 04 (Box 25)
  - United States v. Martinez 1990 November 14 (Box 25)
  - United States v. Mejia 1990 October 16 (Box 25)
    Opinion; Judgment in a Criminal Case; Order
  - United States v. Occidental Chem. Corp. 1990 November 19 (Box 25)
  - United States v. Pieri 1990 October 23 (Box 26)
  - United States v. Pretlow 1990[no date] (Box 26)
  - United States v. Ruth 1990 June 01 (Box 26)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1990 August 03)
  - United States v. Sanclemente 1990 June 06 (Box 26)
    Opinion; Writ of Habeas Corpus; Letter; Probation Order; Social Work Letter; Medical Examination Results; Prosecutor Letter; Defendant Letter; Exhibit; Order of Judgment
    Musculoskeletal and skin diseases
  - United States v. State 1990 July 26 (Box 26)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1990 October 26); Opinion; Order (1990 December 13)
  - United States v. Terminal Constr. Corp. 1990 April 17 (Box 26)
  - United States v. Torres 1990 April 18 (Box 26)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1990 October 01)
  - Volvo Transp. Corp. v. M/V Concert Express 1990 August 15 (Box 26)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1990 October 26)
  - Wakefield v. Samuels 1990 June 04 (Box 26)
  - Walker v. United States 1990 October 26 (Box 26)
    Military operations and strategy
    Military civil functions
  - Williams v. La Polt 1990 November 19 (Box 26)
    Opinion; Order; In forma pauperis order
  - Williams v. Zarick 1990 November 19 (Box 26)
  - Wolken v. Hunter 1990 April 24 (Box 26)
  - Wright v. Craig 1990 November 27 (Box 26)
  - Youngs v. N.J. State Parole Bd. 1990 September 26 (Box 26)
  - Youngman v. Peterson 1990 June 11 (Box 26)
  - Zillmer v. Gross 1990 March 08 (Box 26)
- Papers, 1991 (Box 26-31)
  All papers dated 1991.
  - Andrews v. County of Passaic 1991 May 14 (Box 26)
  - Associated Metals & Minerals Corp. v. Lumbe 1991 April 29 (Box 26)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1991 July 17); Letter; Letter re: publication
    Associated Metals & Minerals Corp. v. Lumbe, No. 90-2149, 1991 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 21794 (D. N.J. Apr. 29, 1991).; No. 90-2149, 1991 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 21795 (D. N.J. July 17, 1991).
  - Atlas Assurance Co. of Am. v. Emar Co. 1991 April 11 (Box 26)
  - Banc Agricol I Commercial D'Andorra v. Reisner 1991 December 24 (Box 26)
    Foreign loans and debt
    Foreign and international banking
  - Bank of Tokyo Trust Co. v. Avalon Inv. Prop. 1991 October 22 (Box 26)
  - Berger v. Humphreys 1991 August 19 (Box 26)
  - Berkshire Corp. v. Texwipe Corp. 1991 January 29 (Box 26)
  - Bi-Coastal Investors v. Westreich 1991 May 07 (Box 26)
  - Bd. of Tr. v. Centra 1991 October 17 (Box 26)
  - Bocchino v. Hartford Life & Accident Ins. Co. 1991 February 08 (Box 26)
  - Brae Transp. v. Crossridge 1991 May 10 (Box 26)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1991 August 13)
  - Brooks v. Beyer 1991 December 27 (Box 26)
  - Brown v. Rafferty 1990 December 18 (Box 27)
  - Brown v. Stephens 1991 July 18 (Box 27)
  - Brown v. Grabowski 1991 July 29 (Box 27)
  - Calland v. Elizabeth 1991 December 17 (Box 27)
  - Cammarata v. United States 1991 May 23 (Box 27)
  - Canady v. United States 1991 May 14 (Box 27)
  - Carlisle Corp. v. Ace Wire & Cable Co. 1991 January 25 (Box 27)
  - Connell Carroll v. Essex County 1991 May 10 (Box 27)
  - Carteret Sav. Bank v. Office of Thrift Supervision 1991 April 25 (Box 27)
    Carteret Sav. Bank v. Office of Thrift Supervision, 762 F. Supp. 1159 (D. N.J. 1991).
  - Castro v. Sullivan 1991 August 01 (Box 27)
  - Ciano v. Am-Darling Valve 1991 April 17 (Box 27)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion (1991 July 18); Order
  - Cigna v. Boise 1991 July 29 (Box 27)
  - Clark v. Goldstein 1991 November 22 (Box 27)
  - Coar v. Kazimir 1992 May 12 (Box 27)
    Opinion; Order (Opinion of U.S.D.J. Maryanne Trump Barry)
  - Conagra v. Woods 1991 October 29 (Box 27)
    Agricultural prices, subsidies, credit
  - Davis v. Worldwide Computer Serv. 1991 October 31 (Box 27)
  - Davis v. Waterfront & Airport Comm'n 1991 January 17 (Box 27)
  - De Jesus v. Nat'l R.R. Passenger Corp. 1991 September 30 (Box 27)
  - Di Felice v. Hoffmann-La Roche 1991 April 09 (Box 27)
  - Doty v. Allstate Ins. Co. 1991 October 30 (Box 27)
  - Duffy v. Liberty Mach. 1991 January 29 (Box 27)
  - Dynatron/Bondo Corp. v. Clausen Co. 1991 January 17 (Box 27)
  - Elkins v. Spanoudis 1991 February 01 (Box 27)
  - Equitable Life Assurance Soc'y of the U.S. v. Houston Gen. Ins. Co. 1991 November 18 (Box 27)
  - Enprotech Corp. v. Renda 1991 March 01 (Box 27)
  - Evans v. N.J. Dep't of Corr. 1991 March 26 (Box 27)
  - Fair Oaks Hosp. v. Berg 1991 January 31 (Box 27)
  - Faktor v. Am. Biomaterials Corp. 1991 May 28 (Box 28)
    Faktor v. Am. Biomaterials Corp., No. 90-2018, 1991 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 11927 (D. N.J. May 28, 1991).
  - Fed. Sav. & Loan Ins. Corp. v. Halperin 1991 May 21 (Box 28)
  - Finkelstein v. N.J. Auto. Full Ins. Underwriting Ass'n 1991 April 24 (Box 28)
  - Fineman v. Armstrong World Indus. 1991 May 06 (Box 28)
    Fineman v. Armstrong World Indus., 774 F. Supp. 266 (D. N.J. 1991).
  - First Princeton Capitol Corp. v. Boulder Prod. 1991 February 21 (Box 28)
  - Fraenkel v. State 1991 November 04 (Box 28)
  - Franklin v. Garrett 1991 April 08 (Box 28)
  - Fykes v. McCreesh 1991 March 27 (Box 28)
  - Gambocz v. McCallum 1991 August 13 (Box 28)
  - In re Gioso 1991 July 18 (Box 28)
  - Gladstone v. Vikonics 1991 July 26 (Box 28)
  - Golden City Bank v. Rutherford Commercial Corp. 1991 January 14 (Box 28)
  - Grant v. Coca-Cola Bottling Co. 1991 October 16 (Box 28)
    Grant v. Coca-Cola Bottling Co., 780 F. Supp. 246 (D. N.J. 1991).
  - Grenell v. Dana 1991 January 17 (Box 28)
  - Grilk v. Goldstar Prod. Co. 1991 June 13 (Box 28)
  - Haider v. XL/Datacomp 1991 July 26 (Box 28)
  - Hamani v. Miggins 1991 March 12 (Box 28)
  - Hamani v. N.J. Dep't of Corr. 1991 March 18 (Box 28)
    Opinion; Order; Application to Proceed in Forma Pauperis
  - Hassan v. Jamesway Corp. 1991 April 25 (Box 28)
  - Hawke Assoc. v. City Fed. Sav. Bank 1991 May 22 (Box 28)
    Hawke Assoc. v. City Fed. Sav. Bank, 787 F. Supp. 423 (D. N.J. 1991).
  - Hayward Indus. v. Cole Indus. 1991 May 29 (Box 28)
  - Henderson v. Beyer 1991 May 10 (Box 28)
  - Holmes v. Arvonio 1991 August 13 (Box 28)
  - Hughes v. Sea-Land Corp. 1991 January 04 (Box 28)
  - Inamdar v. Shell Oil Co. 1991 October 31 (Box 28)
  - Ingersoll-Rand Fin. Corp. v. Anderson 1991 August 13 (Box 28)
  - Int'l Union v. Curtiss-Wright Corp. 1991 May 10 (Box 28)
  - J.T. Hass Co. v. Gilbane Bldg. Co. 1991 March 01 (Box 28)
  - Jacobs v. Feinberg 1991 December 17 (Box 28)
  - Jacobsen v. Bell Commc'n Research 1991 April 12 (Box 28)
  - Johanson v. Arvonio 1991 December 30 (Box 28)
    Order; Order
  - Kay v. Parsippany-Troy Hills Bd. Of Ed. 1991 October 28 (Box 28)
  - Katz v. Peters 1991 June 12 (Box 28)
  - Kemp v. Marguglio 1991 January 10 (Box 29)
    Opinion; Order; Letter-Opinion (1991 January 11)
  - In re Keystone Camera Prod. Corp. 1991 September 18 (Box 29)
  - Lerman v. Joyce Int'l 1991 July 17 (Box 29)
    Opinion; Order; Letter-Opinion (1991 November 15); Order (1991 November 18)
  - Littelfuse v. Bel Fuse, Inc. 1991 April 26 (Box 29)
  - Int'l Fed'n of Professional & Technical Eng'r, Local 195 v. Downs 1991 January 29 (Box 29)
  - Longo v. Sullivan 1991 August 13 (Box 29)
  - Lopez v. Nickolopoulos 1991 March 12 (Box 29)
  - M.V. v. Glen Rock Bd. Of Ed. 1991 May 21 (Box 29)
    Education of the disadvantaged
    General education matters
    M.V. v. Glen Rock Bd. Of Ed., No. 90-2702, 1991 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 21854 (D. N.J. May 21, 1991).
  - Mack Boring Parts Co. v. Moffitt 1991 March 21 (Box 29)
  - Maguire v. Arvonio 1991 July 23 (Box 29)
    Opinion; Opinion; Order (1991 August 13)
  - Malloy v. Turnamian 1991 September 19 (Box 29)
    Opinion; Opinion; Order (1991 October 30)
  - Manning v. Arvonio 1991 June 13 (Box 29)
  - Manzo v. Sullivan 1991 December 18 (Box 29)
    Manzo v. Sullivan, 784 F. Supp. 1152 (D. N.J. 1991).